[{"answer": "0 am on Thursday, June 10th.  Today is the 10th an", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 8, "question": "", "qSentId": 7},{"answer": " Good morning sir.  Can I help you", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 12, "question": "0 am on Thursday, June 10th.  Today is the 10th an", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": "Yes, please.  I have a big problem.  I missed my flight to Korea this morning.  Bu", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Good morning sir.  Can I help you", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": "OK, sir.  First, do you have your tickets", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 19, "question": "Yes, please.  I have a big problem.  I missed my flight to Korea this morning.  Bu", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Yes.  Here they are", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 20, "question": "OK, sir.  First, do you have your tickets", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": "Thank you.  Can I also see IDs and passports for all passengers wh", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Yes.  Here they are", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Three.  My two sons and me.  I have my drivers license, passport, and passport", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Thank you.  Can I also see IDs and passports for all passengers wh", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": "Yes, that will be fine.  Just a moment while I check in the computer So, ", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Three.  My two sons and me.  I have my drivers license, passport, and passport", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Yes, thats correct.  Can I just take the next flight going to Korea instead", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Yes, that will be fine.  Just a moment while I check in the computer So, ", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Let me check our systems for the next available flight.  OK, there is on", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Yes, thats correct.  Can I just take the next flight going to Korea instead", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": "0 pm this afternoon.  However, there will be a $500 service fee t", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Let me check our systems for the next available flight.  OK, there is on", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " What?!?  $500 dollars?  I thought it would be free to just switch the time to a late", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 39, "question": "0 pm this afternoon.  However, there will be a $500 service fee t", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " No, sir.  Unfortunately, our policy states that there is a $500 service fe", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 43, "question": " What?!?  $500 dollars?  I thought it would be free to just switch the time to a late", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Well, I didnt read all of that", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 47, "question": " No, sir.  Unfortunately, our policy states that there is a $500 service fe", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Im sorry sir, but what would you like to do", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Well, I didnt read all of that", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": "Well, I have to get to Korea today, so I guess Ill just have to pay the fee", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Im sorry sir, but what would you like to do", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " OK, let me check the availability for the 4:00 pm flight.  Oh, actually sir, i", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Well, I have to get to Korea today, so I guess Ill just have to pay the fee", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": "0 pm flight is already overbooked.  We cant put you on th", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 50, "question": " OK, let me check the availability for the 4:00 pm flight.  Oh, actually sir, i", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Standby?  What is that", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 53, "question": "0 pm flight is already overbooked.  We cant put you on th", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Right now, the flight is full.  But sometimes there are people who mis", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Standby?  What is that", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " So there is a chance that I wont get to make the 4:00 pm flight", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Right now, the flight is full.  But sometimes there are people who mis", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Yes, you never know until just before the plane takes off whether you ca", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 61, "question": " So there is a chance that I wont get to make the 4:00 pm flight", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " But I have four suitcases here", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Yes, you never know until just before the plane takes off whether you ca", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": "Unfortunately, youll only be able to bring on three small bags that could fi", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 66, "question": " But I have four suitcases here", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " But that is ridiculous.  Im going to be in Korea with my two sons for three weeks", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Unfortunately, youll only be able to bring on three small bags that could fi", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Im sorry sir, but this policy is for the safety of all passengers aboard th", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 77, "question": " But that is ridiculous.  Im going to be in Korea with my two sons for three weeks", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " No, no, that wont work.  Is there another open flight", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Im sorry sir, but this policy is for the safety of all passengers aboard th", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " The next available flight is tomorrow at 1:00 pm.  But after 24 hours fro", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 82, "question": " No, no, that wont work.  Is there another open flight", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " I cannot pay that much again.  This is a nightmare.  I guess we will have to try t", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 87, "question": " The next available flight is tomorrow at 1:00 pm.  But after 24 hours fro", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " OK, sir.  Just wait at gate 12 and let the agent at the desk there know yo", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 91, "question": " I cannot pay that much again.  This is a nightmare.  I guess we will have to try t", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": "OK", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 96, "question": " OK, sir.  Just wait at gate 12 and let the agent at the desk there know yo", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Is there anything else I can do for you today", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 97, "question": "OK", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " No", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Is there anything else I can do for you today", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " I hope you make it, and Im sorry for any inconvenience", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 99, "question": " No", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": "This is crazy.  Next time Im going to set three battery-operated alarm clocks", "docId": "09-01", "aSentId": 100, "question": " I hope you make it, and Im sorry for any inconvenience", "qSentId": 99}]
